

Applicant for:

Android Developer (Java/Kotlin) ~ 2000\$

Dr.JOY 16 April 2020

Lê Văn Huy

Main interests: Android, iOS

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

i have worked as an android developer for more than 4 years, which work well with some patterns such as MVP, MVVM, Singleton, Observer... Moreover, I can work independently as well as work in group with a highly concentrated spirit. Challenges and high pressure in work cannot make me be afraid of. It is very happy when I can study and work with new technology or knowledge. In addition, I can read English documents understandingly, write report, and talk with English native speaker quite well.

CURRICULUM VITAE



Le Van Huy

Android Developer

Date of birth: October 15th, 1992

Gender: Male

Phone: +393807804968

+84918596504

Email: huy.van.le.9x@gmail.com

Address: CUS Unime, G. Palatucci, Messina, Italy

CAREER OBJECTIVE

In 2 next years, I desire to work in UK or other countries in Europe to get a lot of experience in work as well as in life, to take part in some IOTs projects, to become an expert in android development, who can bring solutions with any issue in android as well as in development.

EDUCATION

2018 – Present Messina University

Faculty: Engineering and Computer Science

Major: Computer Science

Degree: Master

2011 - 2015 Hanoi University

Faculty: Faculty of Information Technology

Major: Computer Science

Degree: Bachelor GPA: 6.5/10

June 2014 - Dec 2014 BachKhoa - Aptech Education Center

Major: Android Programing

GPA: Good

CERTIFICATIONS

2014	Android Developer of BachKhoa - Aptech Education Center

PERSONAL BACKGROUND

- Can take under high pressured, high responsibility in work
- Have ability to work individual as well as work in group, can work overtime upon request.
- Be able to self-study and learn other knowledge.
- Proficient in OOP, Java, Android and have base knowledge about design patterns.
- Having knowledge about and doing in Python, SQL well.
- Working in Android, RxJava, Dagger, Retrofit, Volley, Butter Knife, JSON, GSON, FireBase, MVP, MVVM architecture.
- Proficient in English skills for reading documents, writing reports and speaking with native speakers as well as presentation.

SKILLS

Programming	Java, Android, Kotlin
Operating System	Window, Mac, Android
Tools	Eclipse, Android Studio, Tortoise SVN, GIT
Language	English
Others Technology	JSON, GSON, Google APIs, SQL, Retrofit 2, Butter Knife, Firebase, RxJava, Dagger, Retrofit, Volley

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mar 2019 – Dec 2019	SkyLabs Group
Role (Android Developer)	Develop and maintain projects which are related to tracking and recording trips for car drivers: - Receive and process requests from team leader and customer - Estimate, develop, maintain and upgrade projects - Design layout for application - Study technology knowledge for applying to projects
Projects	- Octo Framework: There is an android project framework using for integrating to client application. The project applies tracking location method via GPS in android device help detect a driving car and automatically record the route that driver run through, calculating the speed, distance, detecting the event what driver was doing during the trip such as phone call, handing the phone, and crashing detection as well. In addition, the framework can connect to Bluetooth Low Energy that can support for android device to get location and record the trips.
	- Digital Driver, LVM, ISV, Standard Product: These are the projects integrated Octo Framework for recording the trip when drivers on their way. The apps have functions such as: list all the recorded trips and all information (route, distractions, events, time, distance, velocity) of the trips on google map by octo framework via a web server, make a bridge to connect Bluetooth Low Energy (Smart Tag) with the frame work to support for trip recording. Returning the trip data like scores, distance, time travel. Based on that, showing the rewards for driver. Emergency call function in case driver got problems to send the last location and need a help from support center. Automatically display notification when framework is on duty to alert driver know that they are in preparing, on a trip, or trip is finished.

Mar 2017 - Sep 2018	IPay88
Role (Android Developer)	Develop and maintain projects which are related to online payment gateways of IPay88: - Receive and process requests from customer - Estimate, develop, maintain and upgrade projects - Design layout for application - Study technology knowledge for applying to projects - Communicate to teammates and Malaysia stakeholders to resolve problems

Projects

- **OPG SDKs**: they are SDKs connected to Ipay88's online payment gateways system, which is an intermediate payment link between banks, and merchants with purpose helping buyers pay for online orders by buyers' bank account. In fact, the SDKs are built for integrating and supporting for online payment applications within Ipay88 system as well as Ipay88' collaborates.
- OTP SDK use for integration into applications such as IPay88 QRPay and E-Wallet, it helps send one-time password (OTP) request to OTP system for Ipay88 mobile TAC app to get an OTP for confirming purchases between customer and banks via the online payment gateway.
- Ipay88 mobile TAC: it helps customer manage account that related to projects supplied by system of Ipay88 associated with Ipay88's partners. Moreover, using Firebase cloud messaging to get OTPs or push messages from server after customer made request via OTP SDK, which helps validate the OTP each transaction.
- IPay88 QRPay: this application integrates with OPG SDK that helps IPay88 QRPay as well as other payment applications can connect to online banks, especially banks in Asia. Application helps users pay directly products on list by entering credit card information or scanning QR code and Bar code on product.
- E Wallet: This is an electronic wallet application, which combined with online payment gateways system web services of Ipay88, to deposit money into user's account from banks via credit card or internet banking and it also can make payment products through scanning QR code and Bar code. Moreover, using one-time password system to authenticate each payment through OTP SDK and Ipay88 mobile TAC app. Besides, the E-wallet has feature online trading by connecting with a number of online sales websites.
- **Ice Kacang**: This is a new version of IPay88 QRPay, updated about new design UI, and new functions such as: direct payment with banks, payment via NCF cards,...

Nov 2016 – Mar 2017	Globe3 ERP
Role (Android Developer)	Develop and maintain projects of Globe3 ERP Company: - Receive and process requests from Leader - Estimate, develop, maintain and upgrade projects - Design layout for application - Study technology knowledge for applying to projects - Communicate to teammates in Singapore to come out solutions
Projects	- Globe3 Mobile, which is an android application developed for customers who are enterprises with purpose managing ERP system of their company. This application is connected with Globe3 ERP system via web services and integrated a fingerprint scanner library that help users can fingerprint to register and recognize fingerprint through an android device connected with a fingerprint scanner provided by Neurotechnology Company. Therefore, it helps the company manage both entry and exit of all staffs, which gets exactly time and number of times checking-in and checking-out of staffs. Using SQLite to save offline data and sync it when internet is connected - Globe3 TMS, which is also an android project application developed for managing ERP system with integrated face recognition technology supplied by Neurotechnology Company. It uses SQLite to save offline data and synchronize it when internet is connected. In addition, the application can scan staffs' face via camera on android device, which help register and identify face to manage checking-in and checking-out of the staffs. In fact, the technology works by scanning face and taking picture after, it identifies facets of face and calculates some parameters such as: distance of two apples of the eyes, size of lips, distance from lips to nose, size of chin. Besides, it recognizes emotions of person who is angry, sad, exciting or happy.

June 2016 - Oct 2016	Alticast Vietnam
Role (Android Developer)	 Receive and process requests from Leader Estimate, develop, maintain and upgrade projects Design layout for application Study technology knowledge for applying to projects Communicate with teammates and partner to resolve problems and come out solutions
Projects	- VietteITV, which is an android over-the-top application developed for Viettel Media Company in Viettel Telecom Corporation. This is a multimedia entertainment application using RESTful technology for API services (GSON, JSON), Facebook SDK for sharing video contents. The application help user sees, search video information, purchase via Viettel sim, watch videos and TV Channels through a media player, Moreover, it is able to connect to a Set-Top-Box devices (STB) of Viettel which helps users can sync account, pull contents to mobile or reverse, watch, and pay contents in STB through Viettel telecom system.

April 2015 – June 2016	FPT Software
Role (Android Developer)	 Receive and process requests from leader Estimate, develop modules and fix bugs Study business document Communicate with teammates to resolve problems and come out solutions
Projects	- 16 NaviApp that is an automotive application run on android OS for Pioneer company in Japan. It made from an UI that connects with services API of Car-Navigator system from stack holder. The application displays map overlay, helps user direct way that calculates the distance and time of car travels from starting point to destination, get information about traffic jams, tollways and freeways, gasolines, malls, cars parking, so on Moreover, it supports for setting for car system such as: connect android phone via USB ports and Bluetooth devices

Jan 2015 – April 2015	Vareco Mobile
Role (Android Internship)	 Receive and process requests from leader Design layout and develop projects Study technology knowledge to serve for project
Projects	- Internship in Vareco Moble as an android developer. I joined in project "Android Learning" which was a self-study application for students who interested in learning android language. It contained android lessons, demonstrations to practice in real devices, using JSON, Facebook SDK.

Oct 2014 - Jan 2015	Bach Khoa Aptech Center
Role (Student)	Study technology knowledge to serve for projectDesign layout and develop projectCollect location data for bus stops
Projects	- I made project "Finding Hanoi Bus" that is an android project for user to find bus routes in Hanoi. It used Google Maps APIs such as: Location API, Geocoding API to show user location, bus number, searched places on Google Maps. Using SQLite to save latitudes and longitudes that are location of bus stops.

ACTIVITIES

Dec 2013 - Jan 2014 Warm Clothes for Children - Volunteer program

Role: Team member

This is a volunteer program of Faculty in Hanoi University for poor families in Cao Phong mountain district, Hoa Binh Province, help them and their children overcome difficulties in studying as well as in life.

in studying as well as in life.

Role: Team member

A volunteer program organized by the Faculty of Information Technology in collaboration with the University of Hanoi delegation organized to donate, visit, give gifts to families and students to overcome poverty in Xom Ranh, Toan Son commune, Da Bac mountain district, Hoa Binh Province. For a warm spring, dispelling the cold in the highland and most of the happiness for the people when the Lunar New Year approaching.

INTERESTS

I like travelling to discovery so many different places, especially by motorbike, reading book, playing and watching football match, listening to trance and rock music, taking part in work-group and outside activities.